{
    "id": "ace201d2cd754a39aa186c670bed9303",
    "title": "Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I don’t care …………………. your opinion. I will do what I want.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "about",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9529cee4fc2242b69dbd5f2b0f3b6253"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sorry I broke the vessel – I ………………. help it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can't",
                "couldn't",
                "couldn't but"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f058f3c2379341e2a3a9b1cb40174f87"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who takes ………………….. the sick in hospitals?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "care about",
                "care of",
                "care after"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7bf5b45b551d4d458dd2d49cbe82fe06"
        },
        {
            "question": "Janet is a selfish woman, but still I ………………….. her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can't help liking",
                "can't help like",
                "can't help but liking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0d2df3625a3349918434d3aacd7ad91f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am the happiest woman …………………. the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7859784794a44e399f65557b641a12e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The apartment ………………… I live is very small.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "were",
                "where",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9391578b508e41b1abaee8d2bc3527d8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t paid the fee. I haven’t …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "neither",
                "either",
                "also",
                "as well"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cfa34fb92081488ca9b56159107d822c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Books ………………….. all over the room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "were laying",
                "were lying",
                "were laid"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "db8575f9b37c4a0785c94d6aab8ec7c1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I always have trouble ………………….. phone numbers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to remember",
                "remembering",
                "to remembering",
                "remember"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "06e3a5db2d2b4bff99276067405e7f3a"
        },
        {
            "question": "It ....................... for six hours.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is raining",
                "has been raining",
                "was raining"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1e30dc10e9264e65b16bfa5758a749d7"
        }
    ]
}